Guide to the Duke University Archives Photographic Negative Collection, 1855-1995
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Numbered Negatives
  - Negatives 2401-3100 (Box 48)
    - n2848 Sarah P. Duke Gardens, aerial view, circa 1940
    - n2849 Sarah P. Duke Gardens, by Arthur G. Burns
    - n2850 Sarah P. Duke Gardens
    - n2851 Sarah P. Duke Gardens
    - n2852 Architectural sketches, Chapel, Trumbauer
    - n2853 Pre-school, psychology, nursery, 1953 February 18
    - n2854 Pre-school nursery, psychology, 1960
    - n2855 Pre-school nursery school, psychology, 1952 February 29
    - n2856 Pre-school, nursery school, psychology, 1952 February 29
    - n2857 Chapel choir, with E. Durham Grade School Choir, 1937 summer
    - n2858 Chapel Choir, JF Barnes and Perry Como
    - n2859 Groat, Dick
    - n2860 Athletics, letter from UNC student body, 1942 Rose Bowl
    - n2861 Duke, Benjamin and James B., 1924
    - n2862 Duke, Ben and family
    - n2863 Heitman, John F.
    - n2864 Heitman, John F.
    - n2865 Manchester, Alan K., 1940 September
    - n2866 Gminski, Mike, commencement, 1980
    - n2867 Freshman Week, Bill Milner and Molly Goddard, 1946
    - n2868 Cheerleaders, 1978
    - n2869 Cheerleaders
    - n2870 Cheerleaders, 1977-1978
    - n2871 Chapel, interior, Memorial Chapel
    - n2872 School of Forestry, 1950-1969
    - n2873 Forestry and pulpwood meeting, JH Martin, 1948
    - n2874 Forestry and pulpwood meeting, Dean Korstian, 1949
    - n2875 Field Day, 1984
    - n2876 Field Day, 1984
    - n2877 Field Day, 1984
    - n2878 Nixon, Richard M., 1960 Presidential campaign
    - n2879 Football, Dwight Bumgarner, 1960s
    - n2880 Classes, Jeffrey Vinik, 1981
    - n2881 Class of 1892, Frank Armfield
    - n2882 DU Marine Laboratory, Beaufort, NC
    - n2883 copy 1 Trumbauer Architectural firm, Philadelphia, PA
    - n2883 copy 2 Trumbauer Architectural firm, Philadelphia, PA, Julian Abele
    - n2884 Commencement, 1975
    - n2885 West Campus, aerial view, 1969
    - n2886 West Campus, aerial view, 1935 fall
    - n2887 West Campus, aerial view, 1935 fall
    - n2888 Baker, Frank
    - n2889 Carillon
    - n2890 Carillon, in front of Chapel
    - n2891 Architectural sketch, Chapel Tower
    - n2892 Architectural sketch, aerial view and plot plan of East Campus
    - n2893 Washington Duke building, "Old Main"
    - n2894 copy 1 Founders Day, 1956
    - n2894 copy 2 Founders Day, 1956
    - n2895 Founders Day, 1956
    - n2896 Founders Day, 1956
    - n2897 Indoor Stadium, inaugural game, 1940 January 6
    - n2898 Indoor Stadium, inaugural game, 1940 January 6
    - n2899 Athletics, basketball, 1967
    - n2900 Sanford, Terry, 1969
    - n2901 Student Life
    - n2902 Student Life, 1970s
    - n2903 Student Life, 1970s
    - n2904 Student Life, 1970s
    - n2905 Student Life, 1970s
    - n2906 Pratt, Ella Fountain
    - n2907 Student Life, 1990 Chanticleer page 122
    - n2908 Athletic, basketball, 1989
    - n2909 Doorways and arches
    - n2910 Student life, 1990s
    - n2911 Abele, Julian F.
    - n2912 Architectural sketches, proposed, School of Forestry
    - n2913 WWII at Duke
    - n2914 WWII at Duke
    - n2915 WWII at Duke, Red Cross
    - n2916 Student Life, bonfires, 1992
    - n2917 Student Life, 1992
    - n2918 Student Life, bonfires, 1992
    - n2919 Athletics, basketball, 1991-1992
    - n2920 Student Life, BOG, 1992-1993
    - n2921 Student Life, bonfires, 1994
    - n2922 Athletics, basketball, Grant Hill, 1993-1994
    - n2923 Athletics, track, 1994
    - n2924 Athletics, football, 1994-1995
    - n2925 Commencement, 1995
    - n2926 Commencement, 1995
    - n2927 Keohane, Nan, 1995
    - n2928 Athletics, football, 1994-1995
    - n2929 Student Life, 1994-1995
    - n2930 Student Life, Delta Delta Delta, 1994-1995
    - n2931 Student Life, Omega Phi Psi, 1994-1995
    - n2932 Student Life, House P, 1994-1995
    - n2933 Duke Recycles, 1994-1995
    - n2934 Buses, 1994-1995
    - n2935 Minah, Ted and Bill Jones
    - n2936 Missing from box, note says "skipped"
    - n2937 Demonstrations, Allen Building, 1967 November 13
    - n2938 Library, Gothic Reading Room, circa 1970
    - n2939 Demonstrations, Sanford, 1970 May
    - n2940 Chronicle Editorial Board, 1970
    - n2941 Shears, Randolph M. "Nurmie"
    - n2942 Panhellenic Council, 1970
    - n2943 Student Life, 1970
    - n2944 Class of 1970, 15th reunion
    - n2945 Commencement, 1970
    - n2946 Waters, RC "Bucky"
    - n2947 Student Life, 1960s
    - n2948 Duke Players, Imaginery Universe, 1976
    - n2949 Library, Perkins, construction, 1969
    - n2950 Architectural sketches, Chapel, Trumbauer
    - n2951 Aerial View, West Campus, 1970s
    - n2952 Student Life, 1940s
    - n2953 Student Life, West Campus library, 1950s
    - n2954 Student Life, 1984-1985
    - n2955 Student Life, 1984-1985
    - n2956 Union, West Campus, Dope Shop ladies
    - n2957 Union, West Campus, Dope Shop
    - n2958 Union, West Campus, Dope Shop, 1982 Chanticleer
    - n2959 Missing from box
    - n2960 Missing from box
    - n2961 Missing from box
    - n2962 Missing from box
    - n2963 Missing from box
    - n2964 Missing from box
    - n2965 Trinity College, class of 1903
    - n2966 Cleland, James T.
    - n2967 Cleland, James T.
    - n2968 Cleland, Mrs. James T.
    - n2969 Decorations on buildings, capital, Lilly Library
    - n2970 Decorations on buildings, pattern
    - n2971 Aerial views, West Campus
    - n2972 Duke Chapel
    - n2973 Student Life, 1975-1978
    - n2974 WDBS, 1950
    - n2975 Engineering, 1942
    - n2976 Alumni Weekend, 1975
    - n2977 Alumni Weekend, 1975
    - n2978 Engineering labs, classes
    - n2979 Engineering labs, classes
    - n2980 Engineering labs, classes
    - n2981 Founders Day, 1949
    - n2982 Homecoming
    - n2983 Homecoming, 1970s
    - n2984 Hoof-n-Horn, West Side Story, 1982
    - n2985 Student Life, interior, 1970s
    - n2986 Student Life, interior, 1970s
    - n2987 Wannamaker Hall
    - n2988 Student Life, interior, frat lounge, 1970s
    - n2989 Chapel, 1974
    - n2990 Divinity School, construction of addition
    - n2991 Divinity School, Grey Building, West Campus
    - n2992 Divinity School, classroom, 1981
    - n2993 Divinity School, faculty, Campbell, Cushman, 1983
    - n2994 Divinity School, student lounge
    - n2995 Divinity School, BDs, 1938
    - n2996 Divinity School, Christmas Candlelight Service
    - n2997 Divinity School, first day under new name
    - n2998 Divinity School, 1st graduate woman minister
    - n2999 Freshman Week, 1946
    - n3000 Freshman Week, 1964
    - n3001 Freshman Week, 1964
    - n3002 Destroyed per note in box
    - n3003 Statues, JB Duke
    - n3004 Architectural sketches, Duke's Chapel
    - n3005 Architectural sketches, Duke's Chapel, interior
    - n3006 The Archive staff, 1896
    - n3007 Duke, Benjamin N.
    - n3008 Athletics, football, Trinity College, 1892-1896
    - n3009 Wade, Wallace, circa 1936
    - n3010 Parker, Clarence "Ace"
    - n3011 DU Marine Lab, aerial view, circa 1964-1965
    - n3012 DU Marine Lab, sign
    - n3013 Missing from box
    - n3014 Styron, William
    - n3015 Tyler, Anne, circa 1964
    - n3016 Applewhite, James, 1958 Chanticleer page 107
    - n3017 Humphreys, Josephine, 1967 Chanticleer page 73
    - n3018 Tyler, Anne, 1991
    - n3019 Applewhite, James, 1958
    - n3020 Presley, Elvis, Chanticleer 1961
    - n3021 Jurgensen, Sonny, 1963
    - n3022 Wade, Wallace with Ace Parker
    - n3023 Wade, Wallace
    - n3024 Wade, Wallace and Ronald Reagan, White House, 1981
    - n3025 Athletics, football, Curtis, 1963
    - n3026 Athletics, football, McAfee, 1938
    - n3027 Phi Delta Theta, 1878
    - n3028 Football, Leo Hart, 1970s
    - n3029 Football, Bob Brodhead, 1959
    - n3030 Tobacco Ads
    - n3031 Bubas, Vic and Terry Sanford
    - n3032 Sanford, Terry
    - n3033 Glee Club, men's, Trinity, 1908-1909
    - n3034 Glee Club, men's, Trinity, 1910-1911
    - n3035 Glee Club, men's, Trinity, 1914-1915
    - n3036 Tombs, 1910-1920
    - n3037 Missing from box
    - n3038 Football, team photo, 1957
    - n3037 Football, team photo, 1956
    - n3039 Baldwin Auditorium
    - n3040 Chapel, mid-range
    - n3041 Medical Center Library, old hospital library
    - n3042 Davison, W. C.
    - n3043 Hospital, Trent, Josiah C., office
    - n3044 Medical Center Library, Fred Schmidt, 1947
    - n3045 Medical Center Library, old hospital library
    - n3046 Durham-Duke Tobacco Ads, cigarette packs
    - n3047 Durham-Duke Tobacco Ads, Duke's Mixture
    - n3048 Insignia, Duke Pin
    - n3049 Insignia, Duke Pennant
    - n3050 Athletics, football, 1930s, game program, 1938 October 29
    - n3051 Athletics, football, 1930s, game program, 1938 November 19
    - n3052 Athletics, football, 1930s, game program, 1936 November 14
    - n3053 Athletics, football, 1930s, game program, 1939 October 28
    - n3054 Commencement, 1951
    - n3055 Wannamaker, WH, banquet, 1951
    - n3056 Duke Ambassadors, 1949-1950
    - n3057 Whitener, Fred
    - n3058 Whitener, Fred
    - n3059 Whitener, Fred
    - n3060 Student Life, cabin party, 1940s
    - n3061 Student Life, interior scenes, 1960s
    - n3062 Joe College Weekend, Phi Delta Thetas
    - n3063 Freshman Week, Duncan giving blood, 1949
    - n3064 Student Life, interior scenes, 1950s
    - n3065 Dance, Modern, circa 1951
    - n3066 Athletics, swimming, men's
    - n3067 Commencement, 1949
    - n3068 Aesthetics, Art and Music, Dept. of
    - n3069 Electrical Engineering, circa 1936-1938
    - n3070 Athletics, basketball, first game, Cameron Indoor Stadium
    - n3071 Mary Duke Building, woman's dorm
    - n3072 Engineering labs, classes
    - n3073 Engineering labs, classes
    - n3074 Engineering labs, classes
    - n3075 Engineering labs, classes
    - n3076 Engineering labs, classes
    - n3077 Homecoming
    - n3078 Homecoming
    - n3079 Commencement, 1932, ivy planting invite
    - n3080 Commencement, 1932, ivy planting invite
    - n3081 Commencement, 1932, order of exercises
    - n3082 Commencement, 1932, small program
    - n3083 Krzyzewski, Mike
    - n3084 Smith
    - n3085 Davis
    - n3086 Werber
    - n3087 Weafer
    - n3088 Naktenis
    - n3089 Wagner
    - n3090 Tipton
    - n3091 Griffith
    - n3092 Corbitt
    - n3093 McKeithan
    - n3094 Coombs
    - n3095 Talcott
    - n3096 Chapel model
    - n3097 Chapel construction, Prevatt/Stewman photos
    - n3098 Chapel construction, Prevatt/Stewman photos
    - n3099 Chapel construction, Prevatt/Stewman photos
    - n3100 Chapel construction, Prevatt/Stewman photos
  - Negatives 3101-3229 (Box 49)
    - n3101 Chapel construction, Prevatt/Stewman photos
    - n3102 Dacus, Edwin E.
    - n3103 Davison, WC
    - n3104 Davison, WC and J. Arena
    - n3105 Medical Center, PA Program, 1st grads, 1967
    - n3106 Medical Center, PA Program, 1st grads, 1967
    - n3107 Unidentified white male
    - n3108 Stagg Pavilion
    - n3109 Four Acres
    - n3110 Four Acres, vertical exterior
    - n3111 Four Acres
    - n3112 Four Acres
    - n3113 Four Acres
    - n3114 Duke and NCCU YMCA Cabinets, 1955
    - n3115 Duke and NCCU YMCA Cabinets, 1955
    - n3116 Trinity College
    - n3117 Trinity Park School Club, 1922 Chanticleer
    - n3118 Trinity Park School Club, 1922 Chanticleer
    - n3119 Spence, Hersey
    - n3120 Proposed Indoor Stadium
    - n3121 Cellulose nitrate negative, scanned and destroyed
    - n3122 Duke, James B.
    - n3123 Nixon, Richard
    - n3124 Nixon, Richard
    - n3125 Nixon, Richard, 1960 campaign, Greensboro
    - n3126 Nixon, Richard, 1960 campaign, Greensboro
    - n3127 Nixon, Richard, 1960 campaign
    - n3128 Nixon, Richard, 1960 campaign, Greensboro
    - n3129 Athletics, football, Trinity, Avery and Daniels
    - n3130 McDougall, William
    - n3131 Franklin, John Hope
    - n3132 Sarah P. Duke Gardens, plans, 1959
    - n3133 Sarah P. Duke Gardens, entrances
    - n3134 Sarah P. Duke Gardens, entrances
    - n3135 Sarah P. Duke Gardens, pergola
    - n3136 Sarah P. Duke Gardens, statues
    - n3137 Sarah P. Duke Gardens, statues
    - n3138 Athletics, football, Cotton Bowl, 1961
    - n3139 Athletics, football, 1st kick-off, 1929
    - n3140 Athletics, football, Cotton Bowl, 1961
    - n3141 Murray, Bill
    - n3142 Crowell Building, Devil's Den
    - n3143 Student Life, 1989 Chanticleer page 243
    - n3144 Crowell Building, Devil's Den, 1951 Chronicle
    - n3145 Medical Research Training Program, circa 1960-1961
    - n3146 Medical Research Training Program, circa 1960-1961
    - n3147 Student Life, 1986 Chanticleer, page 107
    - n3148 Student Life, 1986 Chanticleer, page 207
    - n3149 Student Life, 1986 Chanticleer, page 301
    - n3150 Student Life, 1986 Chanticleer, page 313
    - n3151 Student Life, 1986 Chanticleer, page 323
    - n3152 Student Life, 1986 Chanticleer, page 324
    - n3153 Student Life, 1972 Chanticleer, page 148
    - n3154 Student Life, 1972 Chanticleer, page 30
    - n3155 Student Life, 1947 Chanticleer
    - n3156 Dining Halls, 1947 Chanticleer
    - n3157 Dining Halls, 1952 Chanticleer, page 212
    - n3158 Dining Halls, 1952 Chanticleer, page 213
    - n3159 Student Life, 1950 Chanticleer, ads
    - n3160 Athletics, baseball, Trinity Team, 1905
    - n3161 Wilson, Mary Grace
    - n3162 Architectural sketch, proposed School of Forestry, Trumbauer
    - n3163 Architectural sketch, [Cameron] Indoor Stadium (large format negative)
    - n3164 Architectural sketch, Private Patients' Building, Trumbauer (large format negative)
    - n3165 Architectural sketch, Grad Dorm Tower (large format negative)
    - n3166 Southgate, James H.
    - n3167 Epworth Inn
    - n3168 Architectural sketches, Library Lighting, Trumbauer
    - n3169 Chapel
    - n3170 Duke Quad, 1954 August
    - n3171 Duke Quad, Union, 1954 August
    - n3172 Duke Quad, Crowell Quad, 1954 August
    - n3173 Duke Quad, Davison Building, 1954 August
    - n3174 Duke Quad, Chapel Drive, 1954 August
    - n3175 Duke Quad, Library, 1954 August
    - n3176 Duke Quad, 1954 August
    - n3177 Duke Quad, 1954 August
    - n3178 Duke Quad, Chapel, 1954 August
    - n3179 Hospital, 1954
    - n3180 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3181 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3182 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3183 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3184 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3185 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3186 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3187 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3188 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3189 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3190 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3191 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3192 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3193 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3194 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3195 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3196 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3197 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3198 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3199 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3200 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3201 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3202 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3203 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3204 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3205 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3206 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3207 Duke Homestead, 1940
    - n3208 Duke Homestead
    - n3209 Duke Homestead
    - n3210 Duke Homestead
    - n3211 Duke Homestead
    - n3212 Duke Homestead
    - n3213 Duke Homestead
    - n3214 Duke Homestead
    - n3215 Benjamin Duke and daughter
    - n3216 Unidentified, probably Duke family members
    - n3217 James B. Duke
    - n3218 Copy of marriage license
    - n3219 Unidentified, possibly Duke family in front of Four Acres
    - n3220 Duke Homestead
    - n3221 Duke Homestead
    - n3222 Duke Homestead
    - n3223 Moorman, Tee, 1960
    - n3224 Wallace Wade Stadium, 1960
    - n3225 Knight, Grace (Mrs. Douglas M. Knight)
    - n3226 Athletics, football, 1938 team
    - n3227 Class of 1905 in 1903 ARCHIVE
    - n3228 Trinity 1905 Senior Class
    - n3229 Franklin, CP, class of 1906(?)